<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://rojo.space/blog</id>
    <title>Rojo Blog</title>
    <updated>2023-07-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://rojo.space/blog"/>
    <subtitle>Rojo Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://rojo.space/img/favicon.png</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Maintainers]]></title>
        <id>https://rojo.space/blog/new-maintainers</id>
        <link href="https://rojo.space/blog/new-maintainers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As some of you may know, Lucien Greathouse (the original author of Rojo) has stepped away from the Roblox ecosystem. This blog post won't go into the details of why, but if you're curious you can check out the blog post he wrote on the subject. The immediate impact of Lucien stepping away was that Rojo was left without a maintainer, since nobody else was a major contributor and no one volunteered.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As some of you may know, Lucien Greathouse (the original author of Rojo) has stepped away from the Roblox ecosystem. This blog post won't go into the details of why, but if you're curious you can check out the <!-- --><a href="https://lpg.space/post/2022-11-07-next-chapter" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">blog post he wrote on the subject</a>. The immediate impact of Lucien stepping away was that Rojo was left without a maintainer, since nobody else was a major contributor and no one volunteered.<!-- --></p>
<!-- --><p>However, several months later, this has been resolved. Members of the Rojo organization and the folk in the Roblox Open Source Server are now actively maintaining Rojo and its related projects.</p>
<!-- --><p>The only notable change you as a user should be aware of is that the Roblox Studio plugin is now published by a group on Roblox rather than Lucien's Roblox account. You can find the updated download link <!-- --><a href="https://www.roblox.com/library/13916111004/Rojo" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>. This only impacts you if you are <!-- --><strong>not</strong> letting Rojo manage the plugin for you.<!-- --></p>
<!-- --><p>No promises on this blog being updated going forward, since there isn't much that's "blog-worthy" to share. We just thought it was important to share an update on Rojo's maintenance and the future.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Dekkonot</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/Dekkonot</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Website]]></title>
        <id>https://rojo.space/blog/new-website</id>
        <link href="https://rojo.space/blog/new-website"/>
        <updated>2021-10-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the new Rojo website!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to the new Rojo website!</p>
<!-- --><p>The new Rojo website uses <!-- --><a href="https://docusaurus.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Docusaurus</a>, a static site generator focused on building great documentation websites.<!-- --></p>
<!-- --><p>The bulk of the work on this project was done by <!-- --><a href="https://github.com/unix-system" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">unix-system</a>. Send them your thanks the next time you see them!<!-- --></p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Lucien Greathouse</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/LPGhatguy</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>